{
    "id": "9c83518ab59a476e9a315d0b3221c73f",
    "title": "Sentence Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Two and two ………………… four.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either is or are"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a36247602e534b8398613e899a7ad37a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody was late, …………………… .. they?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2d1f3a3cf1d472fa004f1dc661e0e89"
        },
        {
            "question": "A serious problem in our garden ………………… .. wasps.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a8f6725ccda146c3a7be746d71168ae7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody except his best friends …………………… .. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking",
                "are liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d09a5bc67ef74290acbd114f9cb8b362"
        },
        {
            "question": "My baggage ……………………… sent to Paris by mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been",
                "has been",
                "were",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8dfda6ad78c2466fa782789bd12aeea2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Romeo and Juliet …………………… one of Shakespeare’s most popular plays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e90dc8c15b74f1bbd140f6cb70efe43"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Prime Minister, as well as some of his Cabinet Ministers, ……………………… in opening up the economy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "believe",
                "believes",
                "is believing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5b1118017fc46009f08ac50d91e6872"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your ……………………… pretty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hair is",
                "hair are",
                "hairs are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db1e7b1b03a747ae911bbec15b8de9f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "A number of people ………………… trying to immigrate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9479a7237f944950a03a5dffb1c4586d"
        },
        {
            "question": "A group of us …………………. going on holiday next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eafd45bc06864d5e9dc064af0a793e28"
        }
    ]
}